A Finding Aid to the E. P. (Edgar Preston) and Constance Richardson papers, 1814-1996, bulk 1921-1996, in the Archives of American Art
Archives of American Art
- Writings and Notes, 1814-1865, 1931-1983; bulk 1931-1983; Series 4; Archival Resource Key; 8.3 Linear feet Boxes 7-15
  - Diaries, 1938-1980; 4.8; Archival Resource Key; 0.4 Linear feet Boxes 14-15
    - Appointment Diaries, 1938-1976; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 32)
    - Appointment Diaries, 1938-1976; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 1-2)
    - E.P. Richardson's Diary, 1942-1952; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - E.P. Richardson's Diary, 1952-1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Subject Notebooks, 1923-1981; Series 5; Archival Resource Key; 2.6 Linear feet Boxes 15-17
  These are notes and clippings assembled into notebooks by Richardson over nearly six decades. Subjects include the art market, broadsides, engraving, fakes and forgeries, natural history, Philadelphia, photographs, thefts, Venice, and the art of various countries including the United States. Folder headings are taken from the original binder labels.
  Arranged alphabetically by subject.
  - Artists - Adventerous Histories, 1956-1977; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Broadsides, circa 1930-1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Canada, 1962; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Dutch A-R, 1933-1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Dutch S-Z, circa 1933-1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - English XIX, XX Century, 1929-1951; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Engraving 1770, 1780, 1790, 1971-1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Europe & U.S. - Names and Addresses, 1949-1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Fakes & Forgeries, 1961-1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Flemish XV Century, 1955-1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Flemish SCU., circa 1933-1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Flemish II, 1940-1962; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - France, Spain, 1949-1963; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Italy - Baroque & Rococo, 1936-1962; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Italy - Miscellaneous, 1950; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Italy SCU, 1935-1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Italy [?] XV-XVI Century, 1935-1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Museum No. 1 Accessions, 1959-1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Natural History, 1950-1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Philadelphia, 1969-1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 4-6)
  - Photographs, circa 1949-1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Romans - Wollaston 1725-1744, circa 1930-1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Thefts, 1961-1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Tides of Taste - Market, 1953-1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - U.S. Architecture - Notes on Criticism, 1924-1961; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - U.S.A. Collectors, 1956-1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - U.S.A. - Dealers & the Importation of Works of Art, 1962-1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - U.S.A. Dealers - Art Quarterly, 1955-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - U.S.A. Dealers ii, 1952-1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - U.S.A. - 1st Romantic Generation 1765-1794, circa 1923-1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - U.S. Institutions, 1951-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - U.S.A. Neo-Classic 1745-1964, circa 1930-1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - U.S. Sculpture, 1950-1963; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - U.S. XVI-XVII Century, 1950-1962; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - U.S.A. 1700-1750, 1950-1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - U.S. 1700-1710; 1720-1730; 1730-1740-50, circa 1930-1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - U.S.A. 1726 1744 A-P, 1965-1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - [U.S.] 1755-1834, 1923-1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 5-6)
  - [U.S.] 1760s, circa 1930-1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - U.S.A. 1835-1864, 1929-1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - U.S.A. 1865-1924, 1929-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Venice XIV - XVI Century, 1935-1949; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Verrochio - Leonardo da Vinci, 1954-1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 11)
- Artist-Subject files, 1923-1982; Series 6; Archival Resource Key; 7 Linear feet Boxes 17-24
  These are research files organized Richardson about individual artists and art history. Files may contain printed materials, photographs, scattered correspondence, notes, and writings. The most extensive coverage is of eighteenth and nineteenth century American artists and subjects. Other subjects include Canadian and Flemish art, some twentieth century artists, and American architecture.
  Arranged alphabetically by name or subject.
  - Agate, Alfred T., 1954; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Aikman, William, circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Albright, Ivan La Lorraine, 1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Alexander, Cosmo, circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Alexander, Francesca, circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Alexander, Francis, circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Alexander, Harry, 1976; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Amateurs & Unknown, 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - American Architecture, 1934-1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - American Architecture XVII Century, 1950; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - American Architecture - XVIII Century - Formal Tradition, circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - American Architecture - XVIII Century - Informal Tradition - Art Institute of Chicago, circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - American Architecture - Trinity & St. Paul's Chapel New York, circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - American Indian and Primitive, 1936; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - American Museums, 1956-1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - American - Problems of Attribution, 1950-1956; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Ames, Ezra / Andrews, Ambrose, circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Anshutz, Thomas, 1953; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Art Historians & Art Critics, 1963; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Artistic & Historical Period Rooms, 1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Artists & Artists' Lives, circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - The Atheneum, 1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Audobon, John James, 1944-1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Auger, Hezekiah 1791-1858, circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Bacon, Henry, circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Badger, Joseph, 1958; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - B; Ball, Thomas 1819-1911; Barnard, George Gray; Bartram, W.; Beal, Gifford; Beck, George, 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Barbados, 1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Baziotes, William, circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Beard, James H., 1943; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - B; Beechey, Sir William; Bendiner, Alfred 1859-1964; Benett, W.J.; Benson, Frank W. 1862-1951, circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Bellows, George, circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Benbridge, Henry, 1951-1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Benbridge Miniatures, 1963-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Bierstadt, Albert, 1961, 1976; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Bingham, George Caleb, 1945-1976; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Birch, Thomas, 1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Birch, William Russell, 1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Birds, 1945; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Blackburn, Joseph, 1957-1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Blackburn, Morris, 1970-1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Blakelock, Ralph Albert, circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Blythe, David G., 1948, 1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Boilly, Louis-Leopold, 1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Bonfield, George R., 1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - B; Bonnington, Richard Parkes; Bradley, I.; Bricher, A.T.; bridgman, F.A.. 1847-1927, 1955, 1969, circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Boudin, Eugen Louis, circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Bridges & Dering, 1977; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - B; Brook, Alexander; Brooke, Richard N.; Brooks, N.A.; Bruce, Edward, 1948, circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Bouche, Rene, 1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Browere, A.D.O. - California Palace of the Legion of Honor, Thomas C. Howe Jr., 1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - Brown, George Loring 1814, 1965-1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - Brown, John George 1831-1913, circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - Brown, Mather, 1977-1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - Browning, Colleen, 1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - Brush, George de Forest 1855-1941, circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 38)
  - Bunker, Dennis Miller 1861-1900, 1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 39)
  - Burchfield, Charles, 1946; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 40)
  - Calder, Alex Milne 1846-1923, circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 41)
  - California, 1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 42)
  - Calyo, Nicolino; Carles, Arthur b.; Chalfant, J.D. 1956-1931; Champney, Benjamin; Chappel, Alonzo, circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 43)
  - Canada, 1933-1977; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 44)
  - Canada, 1949; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 45-46)
  - Canada - Furniture Tadoussac Hotel, 1946; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 47)
  - Canada - Paul Kane, circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 48)
  - Canada - Pierre Le Ber, 1963; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 49)
  - Caricatures, 1970-1977; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 50)
  - Carlin, John, 1943; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 51)
  - Carroll, John, 1938-1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 52)
  - Carroll Family, 1961; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 53)
  - Carter, Clarence H., 1961; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 54)
  - Casilear, John W. 1811-1893, 1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 55)
  - Cassatt, Mary 1845-1926, 1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 56)
  - Catlin, George 1796-1972, circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 57)
  - Grachi, Giuseppe, 1948-1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 58)
  - Cezanne, Paul, circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 59)
  - Chandler, Winthrop 1747-1790, circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 60)
  - Chapman, John Gadsby 1808-1889, circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 61)
  - Chase, William Merritt 1849-1916, 1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 62)
  - Chasserian, Theodore, circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 63)
  - Church, Frederick, E. 1826-1900, 1948; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 64)
  - Church, Frederick S. 1842-1924, 1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 65)
  - Cinelli, 1961; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 66)
  - Clarke, William, 1967-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 67)
  - Claypoole, James Jr., 1955-1977; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 1-2)
  - Clevenger, S.V. 1812-1843; Cobb, Cornielius; Cole, Timothy, circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Clonney, James Goodwyn 1812-1867, 1943; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Cobb, Cyrus, 1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Cole, Thomas 1801-1848, 1944-1961; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Ship "Connecticut", circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Constable, John, circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Conversation Pieces, 1947; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Cooper, Peter, 1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Cope, George 1853-1929, circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Copeland, A.B., circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Calef, Hannah Jordan, 1964-1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Copley, John Singleton - American, 1965-1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Copley, John Singleton - England, 1947-1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Copley, John Singleton - Wrongly Attributed to, 1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Corot, Jean Baptiste-Camille, circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Corot, Jean-Baptiste-Camille - Figures, circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Coltes, Francis, circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Courbet, Gustave, circa 1932-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Courture, Thomas, 1939-1945; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Cranch, Christopher Pearse 1813-1892, circa 1932-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Crawford, Thomas 1813-1857, circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Crome, John, circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Cropsey, Jasper F., 1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Currier & Ives, circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Dabo, Leon 1868-1960, 1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Dance, circa 1932-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Dana, Edmund Trowbridge 1779-1859, 1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Darley, Felix Octavius Carr, 1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - D; Daubigny, Charles Francois; Day, Sherman; Dickinson, Daniel; Dixey, John; Dobson, William, circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - Daumier, Honore, circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - David, Jacque-Louis, circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - Davies, Arthur B., 1976; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - Davies, Thomas, 1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - Davis, Stuart, circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - Davison, Jeremiah, circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - De Franca, Manuel Joachim, 1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 38)
  - Degas, Edgar & Ballet Dancers and Sculptors, circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 39)
  - Delanoy, Abraham, circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 40)
  - Delaware, 1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 41)
  - DeMuth, Charles 1883-1935, 1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 42)
  - De Peyster Limner [the Painter], 1968, 1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 43)
  - Detroit, circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 44)
  - DeVeaux, James, 1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 45)
  - Devis, Arthur William, 1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 46)
  - DeVos, Cornelius, 1977; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 47)
  - Dewing, Thomas Wilmer, 1973, 1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 48)
  - Doughty, Thomas, 1944-1945, 1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 49)
  - Dove, Arthur 1880-1946, circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 50)
  - du Pont Busts and Turgot Portrait at Elutherian Mills, 1963-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 51)
  - Durand, A.B., circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 52)
  - Durand, John, 1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 53)
  - Durrie, G.H., 1946; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 54)
  - Du Simitiere, Pierre Eugene, 1933-1959; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 55)
  - Duveneck & his Group 1848-1919 [Frank], 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 56)
  - Duyckinck, Gerardus, 1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 57)
  - Eakins, Thomas 1844-1916, 1966-1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 58)
  - Earl, James 1761-1796, 1944; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 59)
  - Earl, Ralph, 1973-1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 60)
  - Eastman, Seth 1808-1875, 1964, 1977; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 61)
  - Edmunds, F.W., 1946-1948; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 62)
  - E; Edouart, Auguste 1789-1861; Eilshemius, Louis; Elder, John A. 1833-1895; Epstein, Jacob; Ezekiel, Moses J. 1844-1917, circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 63)
  - Elizabeth I, 1935-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 64)
  - Elliott, George Loring 1812-1868, 1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 65)
  - England XX Century, 1977-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 66)
  - England XIX Century - 2nd Half, 1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 67)
  - England - XIX Century Black & White, Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 68)
  - England - XVIII Century 1750-1800, 1972-1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - England 1700-1750, circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - English - XVII Century, circa 1947; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - English XVI Century, circa 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - England - Romantic Period, Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - English - Sporting Artists, 1953; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Explorer - Artists & Explorations, 1967-1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Explorer Artists XVI Century, 1953-1976; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - F; Farny, Henry F.; Fenn, Harry 1845-1911; Flags; Flaxman, John; Folwell, Samuel; Fraser, Charles 1782-1860, circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Feke, Robert, 1958-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Fernerley, John E., circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Fisher, Alvin 1792-1863, 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Flagg, George W. 1816-1897, 1958, 1977; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Flanagan, John B., circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Fleischman Article & Washington Greys, 1963; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Forgeries, 1926; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Fossils, circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Foster, John, 1980-1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - France XIX - Classicism, circa 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - France - XIX - Romanticism, circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - France XIX - Second Half, circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Francis, John F. 1808-1886, circa 1943; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Franklin, Benjamin, 1960-1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Fresco Painting, 1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - F; Frazee, John 1790-1852; French, Daniel Chester 1850-1931; Frost, A.B.; Frothingham; Fuertes, Louis Agassiz, circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Fuller, George, circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Fulton, Robert, 1947, 1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Fuseli, Henry, circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Gainsborough, Thomas, circa 1943; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Gaugain, Paul, circa 1947; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - G; Gay, Edward 1837-1928; Gay, Walter 1856-1937; Geerarts, Marc; Glackens, William J.; Goodwin, Richard LaBarre 1840-1908; Graham, William; Gropper, William; Gullager, Christian 1759-1826, circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Gifford, Sanford R., circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - Gignoux, Regis 1816-1882, circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - Great Men of Science, circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - Graves, Morris, circa 1943; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - Green, John circa 1750-1765, 1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - Greenland, 1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 37)
  - Greenough, Horatio 1805-1852, 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 38)
  - Greenwood, John 1727-1792, circa 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 39)
  - Groombridge, William 1748-1811, 1973-1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 40)
  - Guatemala, 1961, 1962; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 41)
  - H; Haberle, John 1856-1933; Hall, Cyrenius; Halpert, Samuel; Hammer, John J. 1842-1906; Harrison, Alexander; Hart, James M., circa 1934-1948; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 42)
  - Hamilton, Alexander, 1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 43)
  - Harding, Chester 1792-1866, circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 44)
  - Hardy, Jeremiah P. 1800-1885, 1942-1943, 1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 45)
  - Harnett, Willliam, circa 1949; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 46)
  - H; Hart, William; Hartley, Marsden 1877-1943; Harvey, George 1800-1878; Heinrich, F; Havell, Robert; Hays, William Jacob 1830-1875, Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 47)
  - Hassam, Childe, 1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 48)
  - Hazeltine, William S. 1848-1892, 1977; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 49)
  - Hawaii, 1962, 1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 50)
  - Hayman, Francis, 1955-1957; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 51)
  - Heade, Martin Johnson, 1945-1948; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 52)
  - Healy, George, P.A., 1944, 1959; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 53)
  - Hesselius, Gustavus, 1949-1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 54)
  - Hesselius, John 1728-1778 - Jandolo, 1965-1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 55)
  - Hicks, Edward 1780-1840, 1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 56)
  - Hicks, Thomas 1823-1890, circa 1948; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 57)
  - H; Henri, Robert; Henry, E.L.; Hess, J.H.; Hewins, Amasa 1795-1855; Highmore, Joseph; Hill, Andrew P., circa 1943-1950; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 58)
  - H; Hill, Howard; Hinckley, T.H.; Hoffman, Malvina; Hosmer, Harriet; Houdin, Antoine; Hubard, William James, circa 1934-1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 59)
  - Hill; John (Engravings after drawings by Shaw), circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 60)
  - Hill, Thomas 1829-1908, circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 61)
  - Hilliard, Nicholas, circa 1934-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 62)
  - Hoaxes, 1961; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 63)
  - Losses & Destruction, 1952; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 64)
  - Hogarth, William, 1947-1955; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 65)
  - Homer, Winslow 1836-1910, 1963-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 66)